喂？
Hello?
- 喂？乔伊   - 菲比
- Hey, Joey! JOEY     - Hey, Pheebs.
帮我个忙好吗？
Can you do me a favor?
我忘记提款卡的密码 你可以帮我去找吗？
I forgot the PIN to my ATM card. Can you get it for me?
好啊 在哪里？
Sure. Where is it?
我刻在提款机的角落那里
Uh, I scratched it on the ATM machine on the corner.
原来5639是你的密码
Oh, so you're 5-6-3-9?
没错 菲比 谢了
That's it! Thanks.
- 你要跟钱德说话吗？ - 是乔伊吗？让我跟他说
- Wanna talk to Chandler?     - Let me talk to him.
他不相信我的电影
He didn't believe in my movie...
他大错特错 这次的电影是真的 …
...which is a big mistake, because it is real. Real.
我这星期来都试着跟他道歉
I've tried to apologize.
若他不让我在电话上说 我就直接杀过去当面说
If I can't do it on the phone, I'll go and do it in person.
菲比 我听到了 请他听电话
I heard that. Uh, can you put him on?
好
Yeah.
- 嘿   - 你别过来
- Hey.     - Don't come out here.
不行… 我百分之百支持你 我要当面证明给你看
I support you 100 percent and I wanna prove that to you in person.
收到 我原谅你 你别过来
I got that. I forgive you. Don't come out here.
原谅我？你一星期都不接我电话
You haven't taken my calls for a week.
钱德 我早都不介意了 咱们是一辈子的朋友 你别过来
I'm totally over it. Friends forever. Don't come out here.
可以跟我们照张相吗？
Would you mind doing a picture with us?
那是什么？
Uh, what was that?
《今夜娱乐》节目
Uh, Entertainment Tonight.
好了 很高兴跟你说话 你别过来
Good talking to you and don't come out here.
摩妮卡
Monica?
抱歉我迟到了
I'm sorry I'm late.
摩妮卡？
Monica?
菲比？
Phoebe?
菲比 真对不起 你到很久了吧？
I'm so sorry. Have you been here long?
没关系啦
That's okay.
你怎么拖了那么久？
What the hell took you so long?
不许你跟钱德说 我遇见了理查
You can't tell Chandler. I ran into Richard.
- 哪个理查？ - 那个理查
- Which Richard?     - The Richard.
理查西蒙斯？天啊
Richard Simmons? Oh, my God!
不是啦 是我前男友理查 个子高高 有胡子那个
No, my ex-boyfriend Richard. You know, the tall guy, mustache.
好吧 这就说得过去了 情况如何？
Okay, that actually makes more sense. How was it?
好极了 我们先是闲聊后来一起吃了个午饭
It was really nice. We talked and I had lunch with him.
怪了 我有梦到你跟理查吃饭
That's weird. I dreamed you had lunch with Richard.
- 真的？ - 不过是跟理查西蒙斯啦
- Really?     - Again, Richard Simmons.
跟上
Go on.
你继续说 奇怪的是虽然他很棒也很帅
The strange part was he was really nice...
但是我对他完全没感觉了
...and he looks great, but I didn't feel anything.
那为什么不能跟钱德说？
So why can't we tell Chandler?
因为他听了一定会发神经 明天就是我们的纪念日 我不想搞砸
It'll freak him out and tomorrow's our anniversary. I don't wanna spoil it.
不敢相信你们交往一年了
I can't believe you guys have lasted a whole year!
哇 我欠瑞秋20美元
Wow, I owe Rachel 20 bucks.
什么？
What?
那是完全不相干的赌局啦
On a totally different bet.
嘿
Hey!
- 一周年纪念日快到了   - 我知道
- It's almost our anniversary!     - I know.
你相信吗？一年前的今天 我还是只是烦人的朋友钱德
One year ago today, I was just your annoying friend Chandler.
现在你是我烦人的朋友钱德
Aw, now you're just my annoying friend Chandler.
- 嗯   - 我帮你买了礼物
- Huh.     - I got you a gift.
- 纪念日明天才到   - 我知道 但你今天就要开礼物 好吧
- It's not till tomorrow.     - I know, but you have to open it today.
我来啦
Okay! There you go!
- 两张去赌城的机票   - 哇
- It's two tickets to Vegas!     - Wow.
这周末的来回机票 一定很完美
Yeah! For this weekend! It'll be perfect.
不但能去看乔伊 还能在飞机上开始过纪念日
You'll see Joey, plus, we'll start our celebration on the plane.
就叫做"飞机纪念日"吧
We can call it our "Plane-a-versary."
一定要这样叫？
We have to?
这是很棒没错 但乔伊说了不要我们过去
This is great, but Joey didn't want any of us there.
他只是怕麻烦我们而已 到时我们突然出现 他一定超兴奋的
He doesn't want us to go to any trouble. He'll be excited when we surprise him.
而且我们自己还有"赌城纪念日"
Plus, we get to have our own "Anna-Vegas-ry"!
"内华达纪念日"
"Anna-vada-versary!"
对 我们该开始和别人交往
I think we should see other people.
我们可以去吧？对
We can go, right?
这是个好主意
Great idea.
好耶 我也要去
I'm gonna go too!
菲比 这是我俩的纪念日耶
Pheebs, it's kind of our anniversary.
少来 休想比照伦敦那次 把我甩掉
You won't ditch me like you did with London.
菲比 哪有甩掉？当时你怀了三胞胎耶
Ditch you? You were pregnant...
真会办 我非去不可
Uh-huh. Great story. I'm going.
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hey.
注意 这周末大家一起去赌城 给乔伊一个惊喜
Listen, this weekend we're all gonna go to Las Vegas to surprise Joey!
包括我
Including me!
你们要去吗？
Do you wanna go?
我应该可以请几天假
I can take a couple days off work.
你当然可以请几天假 因为这趟我也要去
Of course you can take a couple days off, because this trip includes me!
等等 差点忘了 我明天要提报告 不能缺席
I've got a presentation tomorrow. I can't miss that.
我也买了梵谷画展的票 我盼了一年才盼到
I've got tickets to the Van Gogh exhibit. I waited a year for this.
- 瑞秋 不如你我周六再飞去？ - 听起来很可行
- Rach, maybe we can fly out Saturday?     - Sounds great.
好 那我打电话去订票
I'll call the airlines.
其实想起来很不赖 我可以独自在公寓过一晚
That'll be nice to have the apartment to myself.
对 你可以脱光光到处走
To walk around naked.
不是 我可以自己一个人 享受独处的时光
No, so I can be by myself. Have a little alone time.
脱光光的独处时光
Naked alone time.
菲比 我想一个人独处 并不表示我就想脱光光到处走
Just because I'm alone doesn't mean I wanna walk around naked.
你自己一个人住 你也不会脱光光到处走啊
You live alone, you don't walk around naked.
你以为我为何老半天才开门？
Uh-huh. Why does it takes me so long to answer the door?
这趟旅程到现在为止 比起伦敦那趟是好还是坏？
So far, is this trip to Las Vegas better or worse than the trip to London?
菲比 到现在为止都差不多
So far, it's pretty much the same, Pheebs.
好 那我给你们糖果之后呢？
What about after I give you these candies?
- 对 我想好一点了   - 哈哈
- I guess it's a little better now.     - Ha, ha.
好 赌城1分 伦敦O分
Las Vegas, 1. London, 0.
我马上回来
I'll be back.
飞机纪念日快乐
Happy Plane-a-versary.
我爱你
Aw. I love you.
- 礼物能趁现在给你吗？  - 好啊
- Can I give you your present now?       - Okay!
要命 不会吧？
Oh, don't tell me I did this.
我最爱你假装没带礼物了
I love "I forgot the present" fake-out!
那如果"我是真的没带礼物 请你多多包涵呢"？
How about "I did forget the present, forgive me" not fake-out?
没关系啦 别放在心上 等回去再给我就行了
You can give it to me when we get back.
纪念日发生这种事 真是再扫兴不过了
This is the worst thing that could happen.
很好 你最后还是决定 要跟钱德说理查的事了
You decided to tell him about the Richard thing.
什么理查的事？
What "Richard thing"?
糟糕
Oh, no.
什么理查的事？
What "Richard thing"?
用西蒙斯混过去
Simmons. Go with Simmons.
好吧 我昨天遇到了理查
I ran into Richard yesterday.
他问我要不要一起吃饭 我答应了
He asked me if I wanted to go for a bite and I did.
我没跟你说是因为
I didn't tell you because you'd get mad...
我知道你会生气 而我不想毁了周年纪念日
...and I didn't wanna spoil our anniversary.
我不生气啊
I'm not mad.
真的？
Really?
你遇到理查 一起吃饭
So you bumped into Richard. You grabbed a "bite."
没啥大不了的
No big deal.
太好了
Great.
好 伦敦1分
Okay, London, 1.
哦
Ooh.
嗯
Hmm.
喔 怎么会这样
Oh, look what happened.
瞧瞧我自己
Huh, check me out.
我在自家的厨房
I'm in my kitchen...
脱光光
...naked.
拿起一颗柳丁
I'm picking up an orange.
我脱光光
I'm naked.
点起蜡烛
I'm lighting the candles.
脱光光 要小心
Naked. And carefully.
天啊 瑞秋脱光光
Oh, my God! That's Rachel, naked!
不能看 我在看书
I can't look at that. I am looking at this.
好 鲜明的色彩 有力的笔记
Okay, vivid colors, expressive brush strokes.
除非她故意要我看就另当别论了
Unless she wants me to be looking at that.
她知道我在家
She knows I'm home.
她知道我看得到她
She knows I can see her.
她这是在玩什么把戏？
What kind of game is she playing?
也许今晚有人寂寞
I think maybe someone's lonely tonight.
盖勒博士
Oh, Dr. Geller.
别胡思乱想 别自讨没趣了
Stop it. You're being silly. Ha, ha.
真是这样吗？
Or am I?
讨厌
Darn it!
嘿
Hey.
我可以进去吗？
May I come in?
想要的话就进来啊
Uh, yeah, if you want to.
你要我进去吗？
Do you want me to?
当然罗？
Yeah, sure?
彼此彼此
So do I.
瑞秋 在一切还没开始之前
Okay, Rach, before anything happens...
有几个原则我想先说清楚
...I wanna lay down a couple of ground rules.
这只适用于今晚
This is just about tonight.
今晚过后 你是你 我是我
I won't go through with this if it'll raise the question of "us."
我希望这一切…
I just want this to be...
只是各取所需
...about what it is.
罗斯
And, um...
什么各取所需？
...what is that, Ross?
出自于兽欲的性爱
The physical act of love.
什么？你疯了不成？
What, are you crazy?
所以你刚才脱光光 不是在勾引我？
So you weren't trying to entice me just now with your nakedness?
天啊 你有看到？
Oh, God. You saw me?
你脱光光不是在勾引我？
You weren't trying to entice me with your nakedness?
当然不是
No!
你当真以为我想跟你上床？
You actually thought I wanted to have sex with you?
才不是呢…
No!
不是…
No.
No, no, no, no.
你们等等啊 等等我
Hey, you guys, wait! You guys.
这地方比伦敦好多了吧
This place is much better than London.
有个打扮成埃及艳后的女士 给了我这张折价春
A lady dressed like Cleopatra gave me this.
不用一块美元 就能吃到牛排龙虾晚餐
Ninety-nine cent steak and lobster dinner. Huh.
菲比 你又不吃肉
You don't eat animals.
不用一美元 我连你都吃
For ninety-nine cents I'd eat you.
我完全可以耗在这里
I can totally settle down here.
我要的东西应有尽有 就连乔伊都在 你们看
It's got everything I could ever want. Including Joey! Look!
快点看
Look! Hey!
天啊
Oh, my God.
嘿 乔伊
Hey, Joey!
- 哇哦   - 嗨
- Wow!     - Hi.
你的保险套真不赖
Love your condoms, my man.
你们怎么在这儿？不是要你们别来了？
Why are you here? I told you not to come.
你干嘛打扮成神鬼战士？
Why are you dressed as a gladiator?
因为我正在拍戏 我扮演神鬼战士
Uh, because I'm shooting a scene right now. I play a gladiator.
你们等等 可以卡一下吗？
Hold on a second. Can we cut?
我朋友来了 我要休息一下
My friends are here. I'm gonna take a break.
你是在跟谁说话？
Who are you talking to?
导演啊
The director.
就是她
Uh, her.
好啦 我不是在拍神鬼战士 我在这里工作
All right, it's not a gladiator movie. I work here.
为什么？发生了什么事？
Why? What happened?
那部电影因为没钱而停拍
The movie shut down. Ran out of money.
我在这里工作等电影重新开拍 如果真有这一天的话
I'm working here till it starts up, if it ever does.
- 我真的很遗憾   - 这样啊
- I'm so sorry.     - Such a drag.
对不起 没跟你们说 抱歉
Sorry I didn't tell you. I'm sorry.
没关系… 互相隐瞒显然成了新的规矩
Apparently there's a new policy of not sharing.
- 我就知道你听了会有疙瘩   - 你是神鬼战士耶
- I knew you weren't okay with that.     - So you're a gladiator!
他们怎么了？
What's going on?
- 摩妮卡跟理查吃了中饭   - 理查道森？
- Monica had lunch with Richard.     - Dawson?
不是啦
No...
要不然一定超酷的
But that would've been so cool!
是那个男朋友理查
Her boyfriend Richard.
那根本不碍事 你怎么到现在还不相信我？
It meant nothing. After all this time, how can you not trust me?
你瞒着我跟大胡子帅哥吃午餐 要我怎么相信你？
When you go lunching with hunky men and don't tell me!
你说的对 对不起 我早该跟你说的
You're right. I'm sorry. I should've told you.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 这样才对嘛   - 我爱赌城
- Aw, there we go.     - Now I love Vegas.
我保证下次一定会跟你说
I promise you next time I absolutely will tell you.
"下一次"？
"Next time"?
功亏一篑
Ooh, so close.
下不为例 你不能再跟他见面
There won't be a next time. You cannot see him again.
我不能跟他见面？你不能对我发号施令
I cannot see him? You can't tell me what to do.
很有趣 刚才不就是了
That's funny, I think I just did.
你这种态度 我眼不见为净 我无所谓
If you act like this, I won't be around you.
- 好   - 纪念日快乐
- Fine.     - Happy anniversary!
你们别这样嘛
Guys, please! Come on, come on.
这显然是个大误会
This is obviously a misunderstanding.
- 才不是误会   - 你在说什么…
- No, it's not.     - What're you talking about?
别看我 我只是在这里工作
Don't look at me. I just work here.
罗斯？我有点热 要脱毛衣
Okay, um, Ross? I'm a little warm, so I'm gonna be taking off my sweater.
我只是要你知道
Now, I'm just letting you know...
这不是在勾引你一夜情
...this is not an invitation to the physical act of love.
对 真是太爆笑了
Yep, that's hilarious.
抱歉 我不闹了…
I'm sorry. I'm done. I'm done.
昨晚对你其实也很尴尬
You know, last night was embarrassing for you too.
也不尽然
No, not really.
我只是没有那么容易尴尬
But you know, I just don't embarrass that easily.
什么？你根本尴尬得要死
What? You totally get embarrassed.
才没有 罗斯 这是因为我比你更有安全感
No, I don't. Ross, I think I'm just a more secure person than you are.
- 是吗？ - 是啊
- Is that so?     - Yeah.
小姐
Hey, lady!
不管你有多想
I don't care how much you want it, okay?
我绝不会和你去厕所做爱
I am not gonna have sex with you in the bathroom!
在古罗马时代 这不只是顶帽子而已
You know, in Roman times, this was more than just a hat.
是吗？
Really?
当然罗…
Yeah, sure, sure.
这可以用来刷地板
They would scrub the floors.
抹去鞋子上的泥巴
They'd use it to get the mud off their shoe.
有时候下面的马会弄脏 把这个戮进去就能…
Sometimes underneath the horse would get dirty.
乔伊 真不敢相信
So they would stick it right...
我的周年纪念日是这样过的
I can't believe this is how I'm spending my anniversary.
但我带你去个好地方 今天有个人赏我一百美元小费
I'll take you someplace nice. A guy tipped me $100.
- 哇哦   - 耶
- Whoa!      - Yeah.
他玩21点 才一小时就赢了五千美元
He was playing blackjack for an hour and he won $5000.
你相信吗？五千美元耶
Can you believe that?
若我赢了五千美元 我就去加入健身房
If I won $5000, I'd join a gym.
把我的上半身练壮
Build up my upper body...
再用棍子插理查的屁眼
...and hit Richard from behind with a stick.
等等 我何不效仿那个人？
Wait! Why don't I just do what that guy did?
把这一百元变成五千
I'll take this $100, turn it into $5000...
到时再连三翻 就有钱让电影重新开拍了
...and I'll turn that into enough to get my movie going!
祝你好运了
Good luck.
- 钱德 我不需要好运   - 我已经想透了
- I don't need luck. I've thought this through.     - I see.
- 谢谢你   - 谢谢
- Thank you.     - Thanks.
不敢相信 今晚真是糟透了
I can't believe this. This is like the worst night ever.
摩妮卡 你和钱德的关系 有了小小挫折
You had a minor setback in your relationship.
有啥大不了？不过是钱德罢了
Big deal. It's only Chandler.
我真的很遗憾
I am so sorry.
我们吵架的理由太蠢了
This is crazy having such a stupid argument.
我根本不想再跟理查见面
I don't wanna see Richard.
那就去挽回啊
So go fix it.
去找钱德 他八成就待在你房间里
Find Chandler. He's probably in your room.
跟他说对不起 说你爱他
Tell him sorry and you love him.
菲比 你说的对
You're right, Phoebe.
- 谢谢你   - 小意思
- Thank you.     - Sure.
好耶 叫赌城第一名
Yeah! Las Vegas! Number one!
- 所有人都失去了这个问题？ - 走出
- Anybody lose this?     - Coming out.
下注吧
Place your bet.
下好离手
Dice her out.
一赔二 不还本
Yellow 11. Pay the front line!
嗯
Hmm.
我正好要去厕所
So, uh, I'm on my way back to the bathroom.
好啦… 继续走就是了
All right, all right. Just keep walking, all right?
罗斯 你干嘛… 先生 对不起
What are you... I am sorry, sir.
他太喜欢你了
I think he just really likes you.
嘿
Hey...
你知道那个老师吗？跟学生生孩子的那个？
You know that teacher who had a baby with her student?
- 嗨 小姐 需要我效劳吗？ - 对
- Can I help you?     - Yes.
你们有多的裤子吗？我朋友出了点小状况
Do you have any extra pants? Uh, my friend seems to have had a little accident.
- 可以换百元筹码吗？ - 换百元筹码
- Can I change 100?     - Changing 100.
- 先生 祝您好运   - 谢了
- Good luck, sir.     - Thanks.
全押了
That's right.
- 13点   - 再来
- Thirteen.     - Hit me!
要命
Oh, man!
慢着
Wait!
钱德 说了你一定不相信
You are not gonna believe this!
我找到我的双胞手了
I have found my identical hand twin.
什么？
What?
我的双胞手啊
My identical hand twin!
什么是双胞手？
What's an identical hand twin?
听起来像什么？有个人的手跟我一模一样
It was incredible. The dealer's hands were exactly like mine.
就跟照镜子没两样
It was like looking at my hands in a mirror!
你确定不是在照镜子？
You sure you weren't looking at your hands in a mirror?
你不懂这件事的意义吗？我大可忘了那部蠢电影
Don't you see what this means? I can forget about that stupid movie.
我要变成百万富翁了
I'm gonna be a millionaire!
怎么变？
How?
我还没有完全想出来
I don't have it all worked out yet.
不过保证很有赚头 拜托 一模一样的手耶
But it's gotta mean big money. Come on, identical hands!
我得再问一次
Again, I must go back to...
怎么赚？
...how?
这里可是赌城 大家就爱付钱看怪东西
This is Vegas, man. People will pay to see freaky stuff!
好 你愿意付多少钱 看这只手
How much would you pay to see this hand...
两次？
...twice? Huh?
乔伊 我说不太出个价钱
I can't really put a price on that.
你又不支持我了？
Are you un-supporting me again?
不…
No. No.
我百分之百支持你 只是我一时没回过神来
I support you 100 percent. I just didn't get it right away.
我现在懂了
Now I'm caught up.
双胞手
Identical hand twins.
这点子值上百万
It's a million-dollar idea!
- 嘿   - 菲比
- Hey!     - Pheebs!
我找到我的双胞手了
I found my identical hand twin!
你真幸运
Oh, you're so lucky!
摩妮卡呢？你们和好没？
So where's Monica? Did you guys make up?
- 没有啊   - 可是她刚才上来了啊
- No.     - But she just came up here.
那是乔伊
That was Joey.
怪了 那她去了哪里？
I wonder where she is? It's so weird.
或许在跟理查说话吧
She's probably talking to Richard.
你有完没完？
Would you stop that?
你知道他和理查吃完中饭 回来后第一句话是什么吗？
You know what she said after her lunch with Richard?
她对他完全没感觉了 她爱的是你
She didn't feel anything for him. She loves you.
- 真的？ - 对
- Really?     - Yes.
而且她很难过 她真的很想跟你和好 你一定得找到她
She feels terrible. She really wants to make up. You've gotta find her.
好
Okay.
很好
Good.
我真应该开始戴帽子
I should really start wearing hats.
欢迎来到赌城
Welcome to Las Vegas.
- 谢谢 路还愉快吗？   - 对
- Did you enjoy your flight?   - I did.
谢谢 非常棒
Thank you very much. It was excellent.
- 希望您一路愉快   - 太愉快了
- I hope you had a nice flight.     - Oh, it was the best.